<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>
<!-- Food Toxic -->
    <string id="st_carbon">
		<text>활성탄 정제</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_carbon_descr">
		<text> 코코넛 껍질이 주 재료인 활성탄 정제는 섭취한 독소와 중독증상을 완화시키는 약입니다. 이 정제는 독성 화학 물질이나 독극물을 붙잡고 가두어 신체가 독을 흡수하는것을 방지합니다. 또한 알콜에도 작용하기 때문에 음주 후 숙취해소제로도 사용할 수 있습니다. 출처를 알 수 없거나 올바르게 조리되지 못한 뮤턴트 고기를 먹었을 경우 중독 예방을 위해 식후에 섭취하는것이 좋습니다.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]특징:\n
		%c[d_blue]&#x0095; %c[ui_gray_2] 해독작용\n
		%c[d_blue]&#x0095; %c[ui_gray_2] 가벼운 숙취 해소 효과\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_emetic">
		<text>에메틴</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_emetic_descr">
		<text>에메틴이 담긴 병 입니다. 에메틴은 구토를 유발시켜 잘못 섭취한 음식이나 물질을 강제로 신체에서 배출하도록 돕습니다. 또한 이 약은 미량의 독을 포함하고 있으므로 과다 섭취 시 신체에 심각한 손상을 줄 수 있습니다. 이 약을 복용하기 전 다른 처치를 먼저 하는것이 좋으며, 꼭 필요할때만 복용하는것이 좋습니다. 사용방법: 스포이드를 사용하여 1회 당 2-3방울 점적투여 하십시오. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]특징:\n
		%c[d_blue]&#x0095; %c[ui_gray_2] 해독작용\n
		%c[d_blue]&#x0095; %c[ui_gray_2] 구토유발\n
		%c[d_blue]&#x0095; %c[ui_gray_2] 숙취 해소 효과\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_decoction_dog">
		<text>눈먼 개 진액</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_decoction_dog_descr">
		<text>눈먼 개의 심장과 간에서 추출한 보라색 액체입니다. 스토커들에게는 '개털'이라고도 불리며 피로와 피곤함을 해소하기 위한 민간요법으로 유명합니다. 악취가 심하지만 맛은 그다지 나쁘진 않습니다. 크바스 한 잔을 마시고 있다고 상상하면 거의 같은 맛이 납니다.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]특징:\n
		%c[d_blue]&#x0095; %c[ui_gray_2] 민간요법\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_decoction_boar">
		<text>멧돼지 발굽 추출액</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_decoction_boar_descr">
		<text>멧돼지 발굽을 분쇄하여 만든 거칠고 불투명한 갈색 액체로 흙 맛이 납니다. 방사선에 중독되었을때 복용 시 증상을 조금 완화시킵니다.\n\n
		%c[ui_gray_3]특징:\n
		%c[d_blue]&#x0095; %c[ui_gray_2] 민간요법\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_decoction_flesh">
		<text>플레쉬 세럼 추출물</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_decoction_flesh_descr">
		<text>Rank purple liquid that burns the nose hairs on smelling. This disgusting concoction is made from the raw meat and eyes of mutated pigs. Accelerates the body's healing mechanisms by unknown means, and thus the best thing for a wounded stalker recovering from his injuries. However, the taste makes you wish for a bullet.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]특징:\n
		%c[d_blue]&#x0095; %c[ui_gray_2] 민간요법\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_decoction_krovoso">
		<text>블러드서커 맥주</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_decoction_krovoso_descr">
		<text>Opaque, oily red fluid resembling blood plasma made from the heart and tentacles of the fearsome bloodsucker. Causes the body to rapidly produce red blood cells and platelets and hastens natural wound regeneration, making it extremely potent at dealing with bleeding and open wounds. In demand amongst Duty members to seal up wounds incurred when clearing mutant nests. The taste is not too bad either, but the texture of the medicine makes it hard to swallow. \n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]특징:\n
		%c[d_blue]&#x0095; %c[ui_gray_2] 존 내수품\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_decoction_cat">
		<text>'호랑이의 눈' 토닉</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_decoction_cat_descr">
		<text>Fizzy, clear liquid with the aroma of ammonia made from fermented Lurker eye and Cat Thyroid gland. A potent alternative to the more popular 'Hair of the Dog', this drink is used by experienced hunters to chase their prey for long distances and stay mentally alert even after days in the field. However, catching cats is more difficult than dogs, and oftentimes Lurkers will make meals out of hapless stalkers, so this is a relatively uncommon concoction.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]특징:\n
		%c[d_blue]&#x0095; %c[ui_gray_2] 존 내수품\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_decoction_chimera">
		<text>'에이펙스 프레데터'</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_decoction_chimera_descr">
		<text>Murky, bitter medicine made from the heart and flesh of the mighty Chimera. Stored in a flask as direct exposure to light denatures the active ingredients. Chimera blood have high amounts of unknown organic molecules that superficially resemble steroids, which scientists believe grant the monster its stupendous power, stamina, and regenerative ability. This medicine allows stalkers to have a small fraction of the Chimera's ability, but due to the difficulty of sourcing ingredients it is extremely rare. The medicine is also highly toxic to the blood, so extended use is not recommended.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]특징:\n
		%c[d_blue]&#x0095; %c[ui_gray_2] 존 내수품\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_decoction_giant">
		<text>사칭거인 엘릭서</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_decoction_giant_descr">
		<text>Potent medicine brewed from the hand and eyes of the Pseudogiant. If not shaken, sediment collects at the bottom which is thicker than mixed concrete. Legends speak of Monolith fighters who have continued to fight despite taking rifle rounds to the chest or having limbs blown off with explosivesD, completely and totally numb to all pain. Revered as a gift of the Zone.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]특징:\n
		%c[d_blue]&#x0095; %c[ui_gray_2] 민간요법\n
		%c[d_blue]&#x0095; %c[ui_gray_2] 엄청난 피해 저항력 증가\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_breadmold">
		<text>오래된 빵</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_breadmold_descr">
		<text>Old piece of bread partially covered in mold. Not particularly safe to eat, but still nutritious.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]특징:\n
		%c[d_blue]&#x0095; %c[ui_gray_2] 음식\n
		%c[d_red]&#x0095; %c[ui_gray_2] 나쁜 품질\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_nuts_new_descr">
		<text>Bag of 'Dee's Nuts' brand assorted nuts. Contains peanuts, hazelnuts, cashews and almonds in a nice and popular blend. Nutrition value is quite high, and is quite easy to eat on the trail. Especially delicious if combined with raisins. Imported from South Africa.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]특징:\n
		%c[d_blue]&#x0095; %c[ui_gray_2] 음식\n
		%c[d_blue]&#x0095; %c[ui_gray_2] 수입품\n
		%c[d_blue]&#x0095; %c[ui_gray_2] 높은 품질\n
		%c[d_blue]&#x0095; %c[ui_gray_2] 깨끗한 식품\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_poison_0">
		<text>괜찮아진 것 같군.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_poison_1">
		<text>속이 좀 안좋은데..</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_poison_2">
		<text>몸이 안좋은 기분이야.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_poison_3">
		<text>몸이 아파오고 있어..</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_poison_4">
		<text>몸상태가 정말 나쁜데..</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_poison_5">
		<text>곧 죽을꺼같아...</text>
	</string>


	<string id="st_poison_add">
		<text>중독</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_poison_subtract">
		<text>체내 독 제거에 효과적</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_dot">
		<text>-</text>
	</string>
	<!-- 0-25 -->
	<string id="st_poison_mag_0">
		<text>미미한 </text>
	</string>
	<!-- 25-75 -->
	<string id="st_poison_mag_1">
		<text>소량의</text>
	</string>
	<!-- 75-200 -->
	<string id="st_poison_mag_2">
		<text>적당한</text>
	</string>
	<!-- 200+ -->
	<string id="st_poison_mag_3">
		<text>엄청난</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_poison_verbose">
		<text>체내 독 수치: </text>
	</string>

	<string id="ui_mcm_menu_poison">
		<text>식중독</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_poison_title">
		<text>음식으로 인한 중독 설정</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_poison_verbosity">
		<text>상세 수준:</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ui_mcm_poison_verbosity_desc">
		<text>Off: No message indications of poisoning.\n \nApproximate: Rough estimates on poisoning level.\n \nExact: Gives exact poison level out of 1000.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_lst_poison_off">
		<text>끄기</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_lst_poison_approx">
		<text>근사값</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_lst_poison_full">
		<text>전부</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_poison_bar">
		<text>중독 UI 활성화</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_poison_bar_desc">
		<text>Show toxicity bar while consuming items that confer or remove poisoning.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_poison_doc">
		<text>의사 NPC의 치료</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_poison_doc_desc">
		<text>Determines if doctors completely purge poisoning on heal and how.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ui_mcm_lst_america">
		<text>비허용</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_lst_canada">
		<text>Canada</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_lst_scandinavia">
		<text>허용</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_poison_chance">
		<text>해독제 드랍 확률</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_poison_chance_desc">
		<text>Chance for stalkers to drop activated charcoal.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_poison_enabled">
		<text>중독 활성화</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_poison_enabled_desc">
		<text>Enables the features provided by this mod - toxin accrual on food and decoction consumption, negative status effects due to poisoning level, and dropping of activated charcoal.\n \nNote that this will purge your existing toxins. Don't cheat!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_poison_dev">
		<text>Dev mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mcm_poison_dev_desc">
		<text>Enables console printing and allows some functions.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
